

## ADEAN RESSAN LADIA

Full Stack Developer and Systems Architect

#### CONTACT

Email:

adeanladia0129@gmail.com

Mobile #:

+63 928 3078 936

Portfolio:

narraressan.github.io/narra

## PROGRAMMING, SCRIPTING, & MARK-UP LANGUAGES

- Python
- PHP
- Java
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- HTML
- CSS

#### WHAT I AM ABOUT

I started my programming career in 2014, since then I have jumped to different I.T. fields including web, desktop, and mobile dev to further gain knowledge and work experience.

For the past few years, I have experienced working in various designations. I have supervised small to medium development teams, lead and carry out operations and maintenance, and architect micro service applications.

Since the start of my professional programming career, I have worked with startup companies in the Philippines and overseas while having several freelance projects which were able to push through the market.

My passion is programming. Solving problems and to constantly come up with ways to improve people's lives is my job and fulfillment.

## WORK EXPERIENCES

**2018 - Present** Backend Developer | Full-time Position

Detail Tech Ph.

www.detailonline.com Davao City, Philippines

**2018 - Present** Backend Developer | Part-time Position

The Resides Group

ph.linkedin.com/company/the-resides-group

New York, NY

**2017 - Present** Full Stack Developer | Part-time Position

Corduro Inc.

www.corduro.com

Southlake, TX 76092, United States

2016 - 2018 Backend Developer | Full-time Position

Samatosa Software Developer Corp.

www.samatosa.com Davao City, Philippines

2016 BSIT Lecturer

Registrar Admin

System & Database Developer

- Full-time position

ACLC - AMA Computer Learning College

www.aclcgensan.net

General Santos City, Philippines

## DATABASE TOOLS

- PSQL (Postgre SQL)
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- CouchDB
- MsSQL
- SQLite
- OrientDB

# DEV TOOLS & SERVICES

- Azure
- Container Techs(Dockers, Kubernetes)
- VPS

(Digital Ocean, Vultr, Amazon Lightsail)

- Git & Bitbucket pipes

## FRONT-END FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

- Vue Js
- Angular Js
- React Js
- Riot Js
- Bootstrap

## CONTAINER TECHNOLOGIES

- Docker
- Kubernetes

## EDUCATION & ACHIEVEMENTS -

2012 - 2016 BS Information Technology, Database Track

Mindanao State University

Tambler, General Santos City, Philippines

Internship Web Developer | MSU, GSC

Capstone Proj. "Integrated Communication System and Respondent Locator

with Video Recording" - Adviser: Valdimir Oliva, Phd

Soft. Eng. Proj. "ANSHS (Alabel National Science High School) Billing and Fee

Collection System" – Adviser: Laiza L. Limpin, MIT

Scholarships - SMG (Special Muslim Grant)

SWEEP (Smart Wireless Engineering Education Program)

- PPSS (2012 - 2014)

Awards - Civil Service Exam Passer (2016)

PSITS: Outstanding I.T. Student of the Year

IT Engineer of the Year (2016)

2008 - 2012 Alabel National Science High School

Regional Science High School for Region XII Alabel, Sarangani Province, Philippines

2006 - 2008 Dadiangas West Central Elementary School

Barangay Dadiangas West, General Santos City, Philippines

## FREELANCE PROJECTS

2018 Dropscraper

Full Stack Developer www.dropscraper.com

2017 TemplateTed

Full Stack Developer www.templateted.com

2018 Bricks App

Front-end Developer www.bricksapp.io

2018 Bookd

Front-end Developer www.bookd.online

## MOBILE & DESKTOP APP FRAMEWORKS

- Apache Cordova
- Phonegap
- Ionic
- NativeScript
- Electron
- Android Native w/ Java

## SLIM & STACK DEV FRAMEWORKS

- Node Js
- Python: Flask
- PHP: Codeigniter
- PHP: Laravel
- PHP: Slim Framework

Front-end Developer www.poadis.com

## 2018 TIO Listing Chatbot

Back-end Architect

## 2018 T-Shirt Platform Project

Back-end Architect

### 2017 BHS: Biological Health Services

Full stack Developer

www.biologicalhealthservices.com.au

#### 2017 Skedluxe

Full stack Developer

#### 2016 Maestro

UI/UX Designer

## 2016 LigiDex - 1st SOX Startup Challenge Winner

By Crazy Ideas

Coach and App Architect

### 2016 Aerial Surveillance with IP Cam on Commercialized Quad

copters

MSU-GSC BSEE Undergraduate Thesis

#### 2016 Online Election & Mobile Monitoring

MSU-GSC BA&A Student Elections Lead Programmer & Architect

## 2016 Mobits

IT Week Official Mobile App Programmer & Appointed Mentor

#### 2015 OMANSS Mobi

IT Week Official Mobile App

Programmer

#### 2015 - 2016 Tekkies

Programmer & Animator

### 2015 Howe Insurance Services, LTD

2D Animator

#### 2014 - 2015 FX

Programmer & Animator

### 2013 - 2014 BAGWIS - Official School's Publication

Mindanao State University, GSC

Layout Artist/ Videographer/ Animator/ Website In charge